{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856456213","data":{"timestamp":" 946856456213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 229ab61d-1ab1-48c6-81d4-3b5533a1a860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na siku ile hakupata chakula chochote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856496502","data":{"timestamp":" 946856496502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856500099","data":{"timestamp":" 946856500099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856506998","data":{"timestamp":" 946856506998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856511489","data":{"timestamp":" 946856511489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856515301","data":{"timestamp":" 946856515300"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856520575","data":{"timestamp":" 946856520575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856524447","data":{"timestamp":" 946856524446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856528054","data":{"timestamp":" 946856528054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856535815","data":{"timestamp":" 946856535815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856539813","data":{"timestamp":" 946856539813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856544987","data":{"timestamp":" 946856544987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856550161","data":{"timestamp":" 946856550161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856554656","data":{"timestamp":" 946856554655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856560068","data":{"timestamp":" 946856560067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856564612","data":{"timestamp":" 946856564611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856568390","data":{"timestamp":" 946856568390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856571676","data":{"timestamp":" 946856571676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856574953","data":{"timestamp":" 946856574953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856581377","data":{"timestamp":" 946856581377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856588050","data":{"timestamp":" 946856588050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856600902","data":{"timestamp":" 946856600902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856604650","data":{"timestamp":" 946856604650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856608828","data":{"timestamp":" 946856608828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856613019","data":{"timestamp":" 946856613019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856632452","data":{"timestamp":" 946856632452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856638211","data":{"timestamp":" 946856638210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856663001","data":{"timestamp":" 946856663001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" e5e362bb-9dda-49d9-b8ca-3f48161eb8dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856684084","data":{"timestamp":" 946856684083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f2d953fe-8974-4c42-87a6-5fe93a56c217"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856734108","data":{"timestamp":" 946856734107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f2d953fe-8974-4c42-87a6-5fe93a56c217"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856734235","data":{"timestamp":" 946856734234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f2d953fe-8974-4c42-87a6-5fe93a56c217"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856781370","data":{"timestamp":" 946856781369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f2d953fe-8974-4c42-87a6-5fe93a56c217"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856842637","data":{"timestamp":" 946856842637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856843020","data":{"timestamp":" 946856843019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856843512","data":{"timestamp":" 946856843512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856843867","data":{"timestamp":" 946856843866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856844281","data":{"timestamp":" 946856844281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856844767","data":{"timestamp":" 946856844766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856845001","data":{"timestamp":" 946856845000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856848257","data":{"timestamp":" 946856848257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856848297","data":{"timestamp":" 946856848297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856849027","data":{"timestamp":" 946856849026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856849432","data":{"timestamp":" 946856849431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856849737","data":{"timestamp":" 946856849736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856849954","data":{"timestamp":" 946856849953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856850159","data":{"timestamp":" 946856850159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856850488","data":{"timestamp":" 946856850487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856850725","data":{"timestamp":" 946856850724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856853892","data":{"timestamp":" 946856853891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856854305","data":{"timestamp":" 946856854304"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856856852","data":{"timestamp":" 946856856851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856857064","data":{"timestamp":" 946856857063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856857276","data":{"timestamp":" 946856857275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856860798","data":{"timestamp":" 946856860797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856864594","data":{"timestamp":" 946856864593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856865630","data":{"timestamp":" 946856865630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856868326","data":{"timestamp":" 946856868326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856868711","data":{"timestamp":" 946856868710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856869207","data":{"timestamp":" 946856869207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856869561","data":{"timestamp":" 946856869560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856869977","data":{"timestamp":" 946856869976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856870463","data":{"timestamp":" 946856870462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856870697","data":{"timestamp":" 946856870696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856873890","data":{"timestamp":" 946856873888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856873932","data":{"timestamp":" 946856873931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856874659","data":{"timestamp":" 946856874659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856875067","data":{"timestamp":" 946856875066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856875372","data":{"timestamp":" 946856875371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856875588","data":{"timestamp":" 946856875587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856875794","data":{"timestamp":" 946856875794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856876123","data":{"timestamp":" 946856876123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856876364","data":{"timestamp":" 946856876362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856878982","data":{"timestamp":" 946856878980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856879097","data":{"timestamp":" 946856879097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 8baf9020-beb4-4ef8-9026-dd565bc886dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856917218","data":{"timestamp":" 946856917217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856924629","data":{"timestamp":" 946856924628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856926236","data":{"timestamp":" 946856926235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856929190","data":{"timestamp":" 946856929189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856930802","data":{"timestamp":" 946856930801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856933781","data":{"timestamp":" 946856933780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856935424","data":{"timestamp":" 946856935423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" choo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" CHOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856937601","data":{"timestamp":" 946856937600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" choo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" CHOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856939203","data":{"timestamp":" 946856939202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856949748","data":{"timestamp":" 946856949748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856951332","data":{"timestamp":" 946856951332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856954696","data":{"timestamp":" 946856954696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856956273","data":{"timestamp":" 946856956272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856958817","data":{"timestamp":" 946856958817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856960376","data":{"timestamp":" 946856960376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chombo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" CHOMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856962988","data":{"timestamp":" 946856962987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chombo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" CHOMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856964644","data":{"timestamp":" 946856964643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chipsi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" CHIPSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856967146","data":{"timestamp":" 946856967145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chipsi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" CHIPSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856968752","data":{"timestamp":" 946856968751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856971656","data":{"timestamp":" 946856971656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856973681","data":{"timestamp":" 946856973679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856973821","data":{"timestamp":" 946856973821"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" f36a35dc-9914-4ed9-98c1-21ca151c4456"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856990461","data":{"timestamp":" 946856990460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856995258","data":{"timestamp":" 946856995258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856996872","data":{"timestamp":" 946856996871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946856999570","data":{"timestamp":" 946856999570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857001187","data":{"timestamp":" 946857001186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857003839","data":{"timestamp":" 946857003838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857005454","data":{"timestamp":" 946857005453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" choo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" CHOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857007639","data":{"timestamp":" 946857007639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" choo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" CHOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857009245","data":{"timestamp":" 946857009245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857012401","data":{"timestamp":" 946857012400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857013973","data":{"timestamp":" 946857013973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857016328","data":{"timestamp":" 946857016327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857017938","data":{"timestamp":" 946857017938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857020568","data":{"timestamp":" 946857020567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857022193","data":{"timestamp":" 946857022193"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chombo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" CHOMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857024681","data":{"timestamp":" 946857024681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chombo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" CHOMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857026278","data":{"timestamp":" 946857026276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chipsi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" CHIPSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857028669","data":{"timestamp":" 946857028668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chipsi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" CHIPSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857030304","data":{"timestamp":" 946857030303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857033075","data":{"timestamp":" 946857033075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857035101","data":{"timestamp":" 946857035099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857035241","data":{"timestamp":" 946857035240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" fe1d522f-95af-46f4-bd5f-335fbcf5f091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857056388","data":{"timestamp":" 946857056388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b831bb59-e3cd-4486-8de5-93e03c0d85e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_ch-m-j"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857060780","data":{"timestamp":" 946857060780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b831bb59-e3cd-4486-8de5-93e03c0d85e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_e-ch-o"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857069039","data":{"timestamp":" 946857069039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b831bb59-e3cd-4486-8de5-93e03c0d85e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_k-h-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857076967","data":{"timestamp":" 946857076967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b831bb59-e3cd-4486-8de5-93e03c0d85e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_j-n-ch"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857082067","data":{"timestamp":" 946857082067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b831bb59-e3cd-4486-8de5-93e03c0d85e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_r-z-ch"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857085543","data":{"timestamp":" 946857085543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b831bb59-e3cd-4486-8de5-93e03c0d85e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_i-e-ch"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857089161","data":{"timestamp":" 946857089161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b831bb59-e3cd-4486-8de5-93e03c0d85e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_o-ch-d"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857092559","data":{"timestamp":" 946857092559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b831bb59-e3cd-4486-8de5-93e03c0d85e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857096059","data":{"timestamp":" 946857096059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b831bb59-e3cd-4486-8de5-93e03c0d85e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_w-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857099942","data":{"timestamp":" 946857099942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b831bb59-e3cd-4486-8de5-93e03c0d85e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_o-ch-d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857105706","data":{"timestamp":" 946857105706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b831bb59-e3cd-4486-8de5-93e03c0d85e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_o-ch-d"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857121838","data":{"timestamp":" 946857121838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 9289e641-2caf-4ce5-9586-2e30eedfdade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-ch-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857126719","data":{"timestamp":" 946857126719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 9289e641-2caf-4ce5-9586-2e30eedfdade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_t-b-ch"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857130058","data":{"timestamp":" 946857130058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 9289e641-2caf-4ce5-9586-2e30eedfdade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_t-ch-p"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857133560","data":{"timestamp":" 946857133560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 9289e641-2caf-4ce5-9586-2e30eedfdade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_y-ch-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857137307","data":{"timestamp":" 946857137307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 9289e641-2caf-4ce5-9586-2e30eedfdade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_ch-b-s"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857142597","data":{"timestamp":" 946857142597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 9289e641-2caf-4ce5-9586-2e30eedfdade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_ch-b-s"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857149250","data":{"timestamp":" 946857149250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 9289e641-2caf-4ce5-9586-2e30eedfdade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-g-ch"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857152940","data":{"timestamp":" 946857152939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 9289e641-2caf-4ce5-9586-2e30eedfdade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_k-g-ch"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857160770","data":{"timestamp":" 946857160770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 9289e641-2caf-4ce5-9586-2e30eedfdade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-ch-j"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857164374","data":{"timestamp":" 946857164374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 9289e641-2caf-4ce5-9586-2e30eedfdade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_z-a-ch"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857169834","data":{"timestamp":" 946857169834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 9289e641-2caf-4ce5-9586-2e30eedfdade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_z-a-ch"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857176140","data":{"timestamp":" 946857176140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 9289e641-2caf-4ce5-9586-2e30eedfdade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_j-z-ch"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857181892","data":{"timestamp":" 946857181891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" 9289e641-2caf-4ce5-9586-2e30eedfdade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_j-z-ch"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857218267","data":{"timestamp":" 946857218267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b6856cca-81e7-47fd-bdcd-586de43f765d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_ch_n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857224929","data":{"timestamp":" 946857224927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b6856cca-81e7-47fd-bdcd-586de43f765d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_ch_r"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857231608","data":{"timestamp":" 946857231606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b6856cca-81e7-47fd-bdcd-586de43f765d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_t_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857238214","data":{"timestamp":" 946857238214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b6856cca-81e7-47fd-bdcd-586de43f765d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_ch_k"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857244865","data":{"timestamp":" 946857244864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b6856cca-81e7-47fd-bdcd-586de43f765d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_ch_w"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857251524","data":{"timestamp":" 946857251524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b6856cca-81e7-47fd-bdcd-586de43f765d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_j_ch"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857258194","data":{"timestamp":" 946857258194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b6856cca-81e7-47fd-bdcd-586de43f765d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_o_i"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857264854","data":{"timestamp":" 946857264854"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b6856cca-81e7-47fd-bdcd-586de43f765d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_g_k"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857271524","data":{"timestamp":" 946857271524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b6856cca-81e7-47fd-bdcd-586de43f765d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_p_ch_v"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857278197","data":{"timestamp":" 946857278197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b6856cca-81e7-47fd-bdcd-586de43f765d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_z_o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857290305","data":{"timestamp":" 946857290305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" b6856cca-81e7-47fd-bdcd-586de43f765d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_ch_z_o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857319086","data":{"timestamp":" 946857319085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857321580","data":{"timestamp":" 946857321579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857323173","data":{"timestamp":" 946857323172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857327748","data":{"timestamp":" 946857327748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" START_B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857329425","data":{"timestamp":" 946857329424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857331019","data":{"timestamp":" 946857331018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857333320","data":{"timestamp":" 946857333320"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857334911","data":{"timestamp":" 946857334909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857338411","data":{"timestamp":" 946857338410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857340009","data":{"timestamp":" 946857340008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857342183","data":{"timestamp":" 946857342183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857343785","data":{"timestamp":" 946857343784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857347465","data":{"timestamp":" 946857347465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" START_F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857348488","data":{"timestamp":" 946857348487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857350094","data":{"timestamp":" 946857350093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857352247","data":{"timestamp":" 946857352247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857353869","data":{"timestamp":" 946857353868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857361912","data":{"timestamp":" 946857361912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857363517","data":{"timestamp":" 946857363516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857366392","data":{"timestamp":" 946857366392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857368011","data":{"timestamp":" 946857368010"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857370170","data":{"timestamp":" 946857370169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857371772","data":{"timestamp":" 946857371771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857374099","data":{"timestamp":" 946857374098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857375693","data":{"timestamp":" 946857375693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857378373","data":{"timestamp":" 946857378373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857379987","data":{"timestamp":" 946857379986"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857382830","data":{"timestamp":" 946857382829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857384428","data":{"timestamp":" 946857384427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857386646","data":{"timestamp":" 946857386646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857388246","data":{"timestamp":" 946857388246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857390393","data":{"timestamp":" 946857390392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857391994","data":{"timestamp":" 946857391993"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857394479","data":{"timestamp":" 946857394478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857396070","data":{"timestamp":" 946857396069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857398430","data":{"timestamp":" 946857398429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857400025","data":{"timestamp":" 946857400024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857402629","data":{"timestamp":" 946857402628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857404240","data":{"timestamp":" 946857404239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857406665","data":{"timestamp":" 946857406664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857408264","data":{"timestamp":" 946857408264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857410275","data":{"timestamp":" 946857410274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857411868","data":{"timestamp":" 946857411867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857414165","data":{"timestamp":" 946857414164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857415763","data":{"timestamp":" 946857415759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857418069","data":{"timestamp":" 946857418068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857419679","data":{"timestamp":" 946857419678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857422719","data":{"timestamp":" 946857422719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857424332","data":{"timestamp":" 946857424331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857426949","data":{"timestamp":" 946857426948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857428986","data":{"timestamp":" 946857428984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857429078","data":{"timestamp":" 946857429078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857453792","data":{"timestamp":" 946857453792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" aba347f1-fb9c-4237-908d-f445ba83386c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857480348","data":{"timestamp":" 946857480347"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857483800","data":{"timestamp":" 946857483800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857489363","data":{"timestamp":" 946857489362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857498224","data":{"timestamp":" 946857498224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857504506","data":{"timestamp":" 946857504505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857531454","data":{"timestamp":" 946857531454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857540076","data":{"timestamp":" 946857540076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857543965","data":{"timestamp":" 946857543965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857548233","data":{"timestamp":" 946857548233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857552920","data":{"timestamp":" 946857552920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857568791","data":{"timestamp":" 946857568791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857585556","data":{"timestamp":" 946857585556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857601878","data":{"timestamp":" 946857601878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857607368","data":{"timestamp":" 946857607367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857611280","data":{"timestamp":" 946857611280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857614365","data":{"timestamp":" 946857614365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857617545","data":{"timestamp":" 946857617545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857623136","data":{"timestamp":" 946857623136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857628999","data":{"timestamp":" 946857628999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857633339","data":{"timestamp":" 946857633338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857637046","data":{"timestamp":" 946857637045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857640583","data":{"timestamp":" 946857640583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857644001","data":{"timestamp":" 946857644001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857647640","data":{"timestamp":" 946857647640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946857653434","data":{"timestamp":" 946857653434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_024043"," gameId":" de73d513-5f85-4951-8624-71d8bd8f1fc4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}